deskshare.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy

|   | 1. | Personally Identifiable Information, Aggregate Information, and DeskShare Content   
---|---|---  
  | Personally identifiable information (or "personal information") is any information that can identify you personally or can be linked to you personally (i.e., name, address, credit card information). DeskShare will use personal information only in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and will not share personal information with any third party unless you give us your prior consent for such use.   
  |    
  | "Aggregate information" is any information that cannot be linked to you personally (i.e., statistics regarding numbers and types of visitors). DeskShare can freely use and share the aggregate information we collect from the Site for our business purposes.  
  |    
  | Persons who register at the Site and agree to our Terms of Service can access and use services offered by DeskShare, Inc. All information that you enter through the DeskShare site is referred to as "Content" whether such information is personally identifying or not, and our policy regarding such content is described in the DeskShare Content paragraph below.  
  |    
  | Nothing in this Privacy Policy prevents DeskShare from disclosing any of the above-described information to the extent required by or to comply with an applicable rule of law, a request of a government agency or any other valid legal process (referred to collectively as a "Legal Process").   
  
* * *  
  
  | 2. | IP Addresses   
  | Your computer generates a unique identifier (its IP Address) that is communicated to a web site when you visit or log on to the web site. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with administration of our Site, and to provide technical support for DeskShare products.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 3\.  | Cookies  
  | A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser and that your browser may then store on your computer system. Your browser will then return the cookie information to the domain where it originated (in this case, the Site). You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to accept or not. We use cookies to manage the DeskShare log-in process, and to save your password if you do not wish to re-enter it with each visit.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 4. | Site Account Registration  
  | Any visitor to the Site may register at our Site and create a Site Account. All persons who wish to create or use DeskShare, or who wish to subscribe to DeskShare's Newsletter, are required to create a Site Account. You will provide us with certain information when you register (including your name, password and e-mail address). We use this information for purposes related to your DeskShare account including technical support, update notices, notices of maintenance downtime schedules and other administrative matters, or other matters pertinent to your DeskShare products or account. We may also use this information to let you know about other products and services that we think may be of interest to you.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 5. | Updating/Deleting Your Site Account  
  | You may update the registration information you provided us at any time by going to Log-in , entering into your DeskShare account and clicking "My Account" You may at any time delete your account; however, by deleting your account, you will terminate whatever rights you then have to access your DeskShare account and unless DeskShare has otherwise expressly agreed with you in writing, termination of your site account will not result in the refund of any fees paid to DeskShare. Unless you expressly request that your site account be deleted, you agree that your registration information may be maintained by DeskShare indefinitely, under the then-most current Privacy Policy.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 6\.  | DeskShare Content   
  | Persons who create or are invited to use DeskShare may place information into DeskShare documents, files and other data (referred to as the "Content"). Neither DeskShare nor any agent of DeskShare will in any way access or view any such Content except as required to resolve a technical support issue or to comply with a legal process. In every case where DeskShare accesses Content, DeskShare will either obtain prior approval from the Administrator of the DeskShare account, or promptly inform the Administrator after such access has been made. In all cases, DeskShare will treat the Content as confidential information unless otherwise required for a legal process.   
  
* * *  
  
  | 7. | DeskShare Use  
  | DeskShare may gather information regarding access to/frequency of use of your DeskShare products. We will use such information for security purposes and to identify DeskShare accounts that have been abandoned or to determine other DeskShare-related services that may be useful to you.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 8. | Security  
  | In order to protect the privacy of the personal information you supply, DeskShare and its network supplier implement industry standard security features including use of SSL encryption, firewalls, back-ups, passwords and audits. You acknowledge, however, that no security system is completely error free, hacker proof, or failsafe, and as such, DeskShare does not make any warranties of privacy.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 9. | Choice/Opt-Out   
  | From time to time, we may inform you about products or services indirectly related to your DeskShare account through our Newsletter. When you register, you will be given the option to subscribe. If you wish to opt out at a later date, you can do so by going to the newsletter subscription page. Uncheck the Newsletter Subscription Check Box. Please note, however, that as long as you are a DeskShare user, you may not opt out of receiving standard administrative emails from DeskShare related to your DeskShare products.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 10. |  Changes to this Privacy Policy   
  | DeskShare may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting updated policies to this location. To the extent we expand the way in which we may use your personal information, we will provide you with at least 15 days prior notice via e-mail to current registered users.  
  
* * *  
  
  | 11. |  Contacting the Site  
  | If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with DeskShare, you can contact us using our online contact form.
